Hello hello friends very good evening to all of you
and a very warm welcome to all of you so
friends today we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard results
since the results have come out so we are going to
check that out before that if you have
not checked out anything then you can check out
Rally to India Anti along with this you
can record my Skin Technology Student and HCL Technologies results when you put them in For the Self TV if you are
new to my channel and if you have
not subscribed to my channel then subscribe
click on the bell icon it is
important meeting smile so friends let's
start today's video so
friends I have done shopping here you
can see here the company has
recommended Pushtivardhan so here on
Becoming President pitch the equity share
part back is different that is 20% of
spelling and in this challenge I have
opened the results here all the figures
are in the slide here first of all here we
will check out the total of the company  If we look at the total income, it
is 1000 likes from 1463, the
balance has been checked by the doctor, the second one is
cut at
56001, but here a growth is visible
and if we look at the glass, here we can see a decrease
in the comparison of the loop,
if we look at the total expense of the company here, then the
total expense of this company is
from the current quarter cases and the last quarter's expenses, here
more than 100 expenses of the company have increased a lot
and if we look at the last year, then
here the expenses were 1761, so here we are making a message
The Amazing,
if we look at the company's income on a quarterly basis, then the
company's income of the current quarter is
3102.80 lakhs and per 100 of the previous quarter is
5306, so here we can see a pin
and if we look at its last year,
here we can see the last quarter's basis,
here we will see the
company's EPS of the quarter class
six class quarter is 60.47 Seoul  In this
letter, Pace and Austria's was 7.61, so here we
can see the basic one line of last year inside ABS, so friends, here
once we open the company's result highlights
feature to see how the results have been
and on makeup, so
friends, here the performance
quarter Agmark 65 is presented here, 14 is presented here,
once we take a quick summary of it, then we
can see here, here is the
quarter, here is the last ones,
last year's scene of the quarter is here, the
current here was done last, that too was
seen in TI, the quarter metro
oil is getting all these features
on Williams, Prem and here if we
see the voltage current affair
in comparison with the spread, then here we can see video on 1GB,
if
this company is properly important, then here we can
see decline in the current quarter
and if we see
in the last quarter, last year, then here we can
see less Pacific Rim than LA, if
we see the track, then you can see the practice of the power company
here  Decline to see Mahal on
a quarterly basis TV and this is Vitamin
Friend so that's all for today in the friends video see you soon
in the next video